1776, when we founded the light to all nations.
And it's something, really, that an amazing thing
came out of that date.
It's called the United States of America.
In honor of this momentous anniversary,
I hope that all countries who find inspiration in our example
will join us in renewing our commitment, values,
and those values, really, that we hold so dear together.
Let us defend free speech and free expression.
Let us protect religious liberty,
including for the most persecuted religion
on the planet today.
It's called Christianity.
And let us safeguard our sovereignty
and cherish qualities that have made each of our nations
so special, incredible, and extraordinary.
In closing, I just want to repeat
that immigration and the high cost
of so-called green renewable energy
is destroying a large part of the free world
and a large part of our planet.
Countries that cherish.